[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Unlike most animals eyes, the eyes of fish and snakes usually have a fixed lens size. How do these animals eyes focus then?", "correct_answer": "By telescoping the lens", "incorrect_answers": ["By rotating the lens", "By tilting the lens", "By bending the lens"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Hebrew word refers to a non-human, speechless, animated being from Jewish folklore.", "correct_answer": "Golem", "incorrect_answers": ["Lemech", "Robot", "Emes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For which of these animals is the following description true: The gestation period lasts 35\u201358 days. Smaller species have 5-6 babies, and larger species - 3-4 babies. The young are born blind.", "correct_answer": "Hedgehog", "incorrect_answers": ["Lizard", "Fox", "Rabbit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays the character of V behind the mask in the movie V for Vendetta?", "correct_answer": "Hugo Weaving", "incorrect_answers": ["Pierce Brosnan", "Orlando Bloom", "Christian Bale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What strategy for making a man fall in love works according to Gerard Butlers character in The Ugly Truth?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Manipulation", "Seduction", "Lust"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of medical problems does the consumption of raw seeds of the Common bean commonly cause?", "correct_answer": "Gastric problems", "incorrect_answers": ["Eyesight problems", "All of these", "Kidney failure"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many children are left fatherless when The Andrea Gail sinks, and all crew members are lost at sea at the end of The Perfect Storm?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["0", "2", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rain below what pH is considered acid rain?", "correct_answer": "5.6", "incorrect_answers": ["6.5", "6.8", "7.5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For her performance in which 1985 movie did Linda Blair receive a Razzie Award for Worst Actress?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Savage Streets", "Night Patrol", "Savage Island"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which quality does satirist Ambrose Bierce define as \u201chideously appareled after the manner of the time and place\u201d in his book The Devils Dictionary?", "correct_answer": "Handsome", "incorrect_answers": ["Fashionable", "Stylish", "Presentable"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Belle Fourche?", "correct_answer": "The  geographic center of the United States.", "incorrect_answers": ["A new dessert created on TV, which contains three types of chocolate, strawberries, and  cranberry marmalade.", "The resort voted Number One Vacation Destination  by Forbes Magazine", "A very upscale suburb of Paris in which the average house goes for 3,450,000 Euros"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the main components of the stomach juice, which is secreted by gastric glands?", "correct_answer": "Hydrochloric acid, enzymes and mucus", "incorrect_answers": ["Enzymes and hydrochloric acid", "Mucus and hydrochloric acid", "Enzymes and lymph"]}]